R-E-S-P-E-C-T, respect authority
O-B-E-Y, obey authority, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority, come on come on
Authorities are here to help you. do what the say
And everything will be okay, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority
Jesus has authority
In your life when he's Lord of your life
So if you listen and obey
Success is yours today, you will be okay
R-E-S-P-E-C-T, respect authority
O-B-E-Y, obey authority, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority, come on come on
Authorities are here to help you. do what the say
And everything will be okay, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority
Children, listen to what your father teaches you
And respect your mother’s teachings too
Honor your father and mother
Then the Lord will give you a longer life
Students, obey school rules
Respect your teachers, and listen to their teachings
They are here to help you learn
And grow up to be successful
But, first of all
Pray for all who are in authority
So that we can live
In peace and happiness
But, first of all
Pray for all who are in authority
So that we can live
In peace and happiness
R-E-S-P-E-C-T, respect authority
O-B-E-Y, obey authority, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority, come on come on
Authorities are here to help you. do what the say
And everything will be okay, come on come on
Respect authority, come on come on
Obey authority